

Asadbek Iskandarov

Junior Full-Stack Web Developer



+393486442462



asad19990826@gmail.com



https://asadbek08.github.io/cv

Courses

- Codecademy: Python 3
- Udemy: Full Stack Web
 Development Bootcamp
- University Courses:
 Computer Science in
 Python, Algorithm in C, SQL

Skills

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- · SQL and Databases
- Git and Version Control
- APIs and Web Services
- Authentication and Security
- Python, Java (OOP)
- C (Algorithm & Data structure)

About Me

Hello! I have a solid understanding of React.js and Node.js, with expertise in both front-end and back-end web development. By utilizing my skills and knowledge, I aim to develop inventive solutions that can bring advantages to different sectors and industries.

Experience

At Scolaro Consult. 2021–2023 Education Consultant

At Stanford Education: 2018-2021 Math Tutor

Projects

Personal Website https://asadbek08.github.io/cv

Real-estate Website https://real-estate-like-idealista.pages.dev/

Google Keeper Clone https://keeperclone.pages.dev/

Education

2020-present Bachelor of Computer Engeering

Polytechnic University of Turin

2015-2019 Science

ASU High School, Uzbekistan

Languages

English C1

Italian A2

Uzbek Native